>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们谈谈下一个抽象的操作。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's talk then
about the next abstract operation.
这叫 toString
It's called toString.
toString 抽象操作会执行它的声音。
The toString abstract operation
does what it sounds like.
这在标签上是描述性的
It's very descriptive on the label.
它具有任何价值和价值
It takes any value and
以字符串形式给出该值的表示。
gives us the representation
of that value in string form.
几乎所有你能想象的价值都至少有一些
And almost every value that you
can imagine has at least some
字符串形式的表示形式。
kind of representation in string form.
顺便说下括号里是实际的 spec 节
By the way in the parentheses I'm
noting the actual spec sections as they
目前的版本目前在 ES2018的版本中。
exist currently in the version
at this moment which is ES2018.
他们投票给了 ES2019 规范，今年晚些时候会出来。
They voted on the ES2019 spec and it'll
come out a little bit later this year.
希望这些节号中的大部分都不会改变
Hopefully most of these section
numbers won't change but those are for
ES2018 规范。
the ES2018 specs.
好的， toString opperation。
Okay so the toString opperation.
让我给你们展示一些细节让我给你们展示一些东西
Boiling down a bunch of details let me
just show you some examples of things and
以字符串表示形式最终生成的内容。
what they end up producing
as a string representation.
而最重要的部分正是你所期望的。
And for the most part these
are exactly what you'd expect.
如果您的值为空，并且您结束了该 toString
If you had a null value and
you ended up doing that toString
以某种方式进行抽象操作，您将获得空引号。
abstract operation in some way,
you'd get quote null.
与未定义的，真实的假，浮点数，甚至是零相同。
Same thing with undefined, true false,
floating point numbers, even the zero.
当我们看到负零点的时候，情况有点奇怪，记住。
Things get a little strange when we look
at the negative zero, remember that.
我们已经看到它撒谎了负零点的 toString 操作
We already saw that it lies, the toString
operation for negative zero lies and
生成报价零。
produces a quote, zero.
这就是其中一个角落
So that's one of the corner cases and
我们会在角落里多聊聊
we'll talk more about
corner cases in a bit.
好吧如果我们在一个物体上调用 toString 它将会调用
All right so if we call toString on
an object remember it's going to invoke
带有字符串提示的 toPrimitive 。
the toPrimitive with the string hint.
那么这会给我们什么呢 ?
So what's that going to give us?
记住要先把 toString 结尾
Remember that's gonna end up
calling toString first and
如果它存在然后就会使用 valueOf
if it's present and
then it's going to use valueOf.
这就是它的顺序
That's the order that it does.
那在某些特定对象上是什么样的
So what's that gonna look like
on some particular object?
那么，如果是数组，那么数组具有缺省 toString，
Well, if it's an array, for example,
arrays have a default toString,
这将对数组的表示进行序列化。
which serializes
the representation of the array.
有点奇怪的序列化
It's a bit of a strange serialization,
因为他们要离开支架了
in my opinion,
because they're leaving off the brackets.
因此，如果您对空数组进行序列化，那么将获得空字符串。
So if you serialized a empty array,
you get an empty string.
我觉得这是个愚蠢的决定
I think that was a really dumb decision.
我不知道他们为什么要离开支架
I don't know why they
left off the brackets.
因为事实证明，有很多东西可以序列化为弦。
Because it turns out, there's a bunch of
things that can serialize to strings.
我该怎么知道它是空的阵列吗
So how am I supposed to know
whether it was an empty array?
不过，这就是它的运作方式。
But nevertheless, this is how it works.
数组中的内置 toString 将离开方括号。
The built-in toString on arrays
leaves off the brackets.
如果我们的数组中有一些内容
If we have an array with
some contents in it,
它会显示那些内容，除非它们是空的和未定义的。
it'll show those contents unless
they're null and undefined.
这甚至是一个奇怪的， toString 的定义。
And this is even weirder,
the toString definition for this.
我那天其实就是在看那个规格，我就像在地球上
I actually was just reading the spec the
other day and I was like why on earth they
当它们在数组中出现时，此值，空值和未定义的值就会被排除。
do this, nulls and undefines, when they
show up in arrays just get left out.
我是说他们现在在那儿
I mean they're there presently.
你可以看到那里有个逗号
You can see there's a comma there.
他们现在就在那里，但是
They're there presently
in terms of position, but
它们没有表示为空值，并且未定义空值和
they're not represented as nulls and
undefines the way null and
在 toStrings do时取消定义。
undefine when toStrings do.
我认为一个奇怪的矛盾
In my opinion, a bizarre inconsistency.
本质上，排列成膜就好像你可以在 dev 中使用它
Essentially, array to stringification is
like maybe you could use it in the dev
但我不会在节目里用这种东西
console but I would never use something
like this in my program because all these
它的行为怪异的角落
weird corner cases of its behavior.
>> Kyle Simpson: 关于对象的内容 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What about on objects?
我相信你们都看过类似的支架对象物
I'm sure you've all seen the bracket
object object thing which is like,
那到底是什么
what on earth is that?
原型对象上的缺省 toString 为
The default toString on
the object of prototype is to
做整个支架的事
do that whole bracket thing.
这，让我在这里仅仅是一个微小的瞬间，地球为什么会这样做呢 ?
And this, let me just rant for just
a micro moment here, why on earth did they
将方括号放在方括号中，并将方括号放置在对象上吗 ?
leave off the square brackets for arrays
and put the square brackets on objects?
有人向我解释一下地球上的东西
Somebody explain that to me,
what on earth.
债券人
Bonkers.
好吧但要回到现实中
Okay but back to reality for a moment.
它是方括号，它是小写对象和
It does the square brackets,
it does a lower case object and
然后把这个叫做字符串标签的东西放进去。
then it puts in this thing
which is called the string tag.
事实证明你可以覆盖整个
And it turns out you can actually
override the string tag for
任何使用 ES6 符号的定制对象。
any of your own custom
objects using an ES6 symbol.
你可以，它叫做 toString 标记，你可以改变它。
You can, it's called toString tag and
you can change it.
所以你可以把它从那个串里改
So you could change it from saying
Object there in that string to saying
我最喜欢的号码或是你想说的
my favorite number, or
whatever you want it to say.
这是一个元编程，但它是可以做到的。
That's a meta programming thing but
it is possible to do.
因此，对象是所有缺省对象的缺省字符串标记。
So that Object there is the default
string tag for all default objects.
然后 toString 方法采用该字符串标记和
And then the toString method
takes that string tag and
把其他垃圾包裹在附近
wraps this other junk around it.
如果您使用 toString 方法，那么可以完全控制
If you over ride the toString method,
you can completely control
你想让你的物体看起来像什么
what you want the stringtification
of your object to look like.
在这种情况下，我要把它变成一个字符串 X。
In this case, I'm making it turn,
return just a string X.
我用了这个方法，我定义了 toString 方法，
I have used this by the way,
I have defined a toString method,
但我把它定义成了一个吸气剂
but I've defined it as a getter so
它可以在字符串标记中动态返回。
that it can be dynamically
returned in the string tag.
我用这样的方式来界定这一点
I've defined this in such a way so
that, on an object,
我一直都不这么做
and I don't do this all the time.
但如果我想了解一个物体的背景
But if I'm trying to understand
what's in the context of an object,
对象对象对我无效。
object Object is not helpful to me.
但您可以覆盖该对象，并将其告知 JSON-stringify 对象和
But you can override it, and
tell it to JSON-stringify the object and
打印那些结果那就更棒了
print those results,
and that is much nicer.
因此，您可以覆盖 toString，
So you can override a toString,
或字符串标记，以帮助您在 dev 控制台中使用。
or the string tag,
to help you in the dev console.
但这不是我通常会做的
But again, this is not the sort of
metaprogramming I would typically do
我的节目里有很多
much in my programs.